# **Charlotte Clark**

Los Angeles, CA 90025 • 623 236 6390 • charlotte.clark@alumni.usc.edu

https://charlocc.github.io/charlotteportfolio/

https://github.com/charlocc

https://www.linkedin.com/in/charlotte-clark-ba486213a/

#### **SUMMARY**

Skilled full-stack web developer with 2+ years of experience in behavioral health, including marketing and social media for a behavioral health provider, a role which requires a broad approach to problem solving and ability to work collaboratively with a team.

### **SKILLS & INTERESTS**

Languages: JavaScript, HTML, CSS

Proficient in: Node.js, Express.js, Handlebars.js, React.js, bcrypt, Heroku, Mysql2, Adobe Suite

#### RECENT PROJECTS

**Activity Planner** – Find campgrounds and national parks near you, <a href="https://charlocc.github.io/activityplanner/">https://charlocc.github.io/activityplanner/</a> Aug. 2021

- Team Project: I connected two APIs and set up local storage, as well as the front-end javascript **#bigtechblog** A blog for discussing everything tech related, <a href="https://radiant-ocean-47580.herokuapp.com/">https://radiant-ocean-47580.herokuapp.com/</a> Sept. 2021
- Individual Project: Demonstrates Handlebars.js, Heroku, Express.js, bcrypt **re:mind** Daily health and wellness tracking, <a href="https://re-mind-app.herokuapp.com/">https://re-mind-app.herokuapp.com/</a> Oct 2021
  - Team Project: I wrote the backend for the MERN framework and created the dashboard where user input data renders

## WORK EXPERIENCE

Pyles and Associates – Marketing Manager, Los Angeles, CA

2020 - Present

- Track weekly analytics and established a strategy to grow our audience
- Edit weekly videos and blogs
- Create daily posts across all platforms
- Lead marketing team meetings and coordinate content creation

Pyles and Associates – Senior Therapist, Los Angeles, CA

2019 - 2021

- Conduct monthly evaluations and trainings with each behavior technician I oversee during weekly overlaps
- Track data on each client's progress
- Support program managers by troubleshooting barriers to client and staff skill acquisition
- Implement behavioral support plans for children with developmental disabilities

**Expeditors International of Washington** – Air Export Intern, Los Angeles, CA

2018

· Scheduled and coordinated international freight by air

**Hurry Curry of Tokyo** – Waitress, Seattle, WA

2017

# **EDUCATION**

# University of California, Los Angeles

2021

The Full Stack Coding Bootcamp Certificate at UCLA Extension

University of Southern California, Dornsife College of Letters Arts, and Sciences

2016-2020

B.A. International Relations and Minor in French